

# **Profile**

My name is Erick Hernandez and I'm from Mexico City.

I enjoy creating things that live on the internet. My interest in web development started in 2018 when I decided to try building web and mobile apps. Turns out hacking a custom re-blog button together taught me a lot about coding!

Fast-forward to today, and I've had the privilege of working as a freelance developer at <u>an advertising agency</u>, <u>a start-up</u>. My main focus these days is building accessible, inclusive products and digital experiences for a variety of clients.

# **Employment History**

# Front-end Developer, Kaiber

JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

- Developing and maintaining web applications using React.js and other related technologies.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams including designers, product managers, and other developers to create high-quality products.
- Implementing responsive design and ensuring cross-browser compatibility.
- Participating in code reviews and providing constructive feedback to other developers.

# Front-end Developer, Pixelbot, 600-212 King St. W., Toronto, ON, Canada

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- Developing and maintaining web applications using React.js and other related technologies.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams including designers, product managers, and other developers to create high-quality products.
- Implementing responsive design and ensuring cross-browser compatibility.
- Participating in code reviews and providing constructive feedback to other developers.

# Front-end Developer, Mullenlowe, 245 8th Avenue #1030, NYC 10011

JANUARY 2020 - JULY 2021

- Developing and maintaining web applications using React.js and other related technologies.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams including designers, product managers, and other developers to create high-quality products.
- Implementing responsive design and ensuring cross-browser compatibility.
- Participating in code reviews and providing constructive feedback to other developers.

# **Education**

certificate, Universidad Insurgentes, Mexico City

JANUARY 2017 - JANUARY 2020

Software and Network Engineering

#### **Details**

Mexico City +525564786032 yerickk8@gmail.com

## Links

<u>Portfolio</u>

Portfolio 3D

## **Skills**

React

**React Native** 

AngularJS

JavaScript

Node.js

Express.js

jQuery

Python

Django

HTML & CSS

Bootstrap

Git

GitHub

MySQL

MongoDB

## Languages

English

### **Hobbies**

reading - exercise- music